<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Samudra&#39;s thoughts on</title>
    <link>http://www.samudranb.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Samudra&#39;s thoughts on</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 17:01:45 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.samudranb.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Spoiler Free Review of My Favorite Tv Police Procedural Comedy Episode Ever</title>
      <link>http://www.samudranb.com/post/spoiler-free-review-of-my-favorite-tv-police-procedural-comedy-episode-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jun 2018 17:01:45 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.samudranb.com/post/spoiler-free-review-of-my-favorite-tv-police-procedural-comedy-episode-ever/</guid>
      <description>Brooklyn Nine Nine S05 E14 has got to be one of the best TV Comedy episodes ever.
It’s about triumph of Good over Evil. It’s about honest cops getting the bad guy using legal means.
It’s about a lovely pseudo-parent-child relationship. It’s about a person who wants the approval of their parent-figure.
It’s funny. It constantly keeps you sniggering at a pace that is the right sniggering pace. And it has an inside joke that the characters laugh at, unlike most other jokes in this series, maybe even all comedy shows, which are at some character’s expense.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2001 - A Space Odyssey - A Review</title>
      <link>http://www.samudranb.com/post/2001---a-space-odyssey---a-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 May 2018 15:26:18 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.samudranb.com/post/2001---a-space-odyssey---a-review/</guid>
      <description>I am going to assume that you have already seen this movie, and are open to discussing what would otherwise be spoilers. Turn around NOW if you have not seen this movie yet!
Also, I have not yet read the books or watched the other movies, so some of my thoughts below might be divergent from what was uncovered in those later works.
What a great weekend! It all started with a session on focus to fix the issues with my blog deployment - something had broken when I had deployed Hugo the last time and I hadn&amp;rsquo;t been able to fix it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Penny For My ADD Thoughts</title>
      <link>http://www.samudranb.com/post/a-penny-for-my-add-thoughts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 May 2018 15:07:06 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.samudranb.com/post/a-penny-for-my-add-thoughts/</guid>
      <description>If I wrote a book, it would be called APFMAT. And I&amp;rsquo;d sell it for a penny.
I wonder what I would write in it maybe I will write about me wondering what it must be like in other people&amp;rsquo;s heads I was watching Legion the other day and wished I was a telepath like the main character what an awesome show that is turning out to be I hope they don&amp;rsquo;t screw it up like they did Heroes so far it looks very promising I especially like the sound design and the camerawork like in that scene where they reveal that things are not really what they seem to be and he is actually being interrogated by not-a-cop I kept trying to remember where I had seen that actor before and realized he had played the disgraced journalist in The Newsroom man Aaron Sorkin has an amazing writing staff that reminds me I have to watch The West Wing it is supposed to be the best tv show about politics ever speaking of which why is Rahul Gandhi such an easy target he really needs to hire a better branding and PR team &amp;ndash;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Death and Rebirth</title>
      <link>http://www.samudranb.com/post/death-and-rebirth/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 May 2018 16:57:29 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.samudranb.com/post/death-and-rebirth/</guid>
      <description>The Intention Of late, I have been thinking about life and death and life beyond death.
I now believe that creating everlasting art is the only way to achieve true immortality. Art (and progeny, to a certain extent) is the only way to live beyond the grave.
And since I am not yet anywhere close to creating the kind of art that would qualify even for consideration in the &amp;ldquo;everlasting&amp;rdquo; category, I decided to be more intentional about whatever I do create.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>